

Marian

Kostadinov

Contact

Address:

Brucker Bundesstrasse 38, Furth, Austria

Email:

champion5star247963@gmail.com

Skype:

live:.cid.e07bcb612fe88d1b

Skills

- React JS
- React Native
- Vue.js
- Express.js
- Django
- Laravel
- Node.js
- Javascript
- Typescript
- Python
- PHP
- MongoDB
- PostgreSQL
- MySQL

Language

English C1

Summary

Senior full-stack developer with over 7 years of experience in software development across various industries, with the 5 most recent years focused on React and TypeScript. I am well-respected amongst industry-leading companies as a skilled developer who truly understands the client infrastructure and pain points. I also have the hands-on, technical aptitude needed to design and build out solutions.

Skill Highlights

- UX/UI
- API building and Integration
- Soket IO
- Database design
- Good communication

Experience

Lead Developer - 05/2019 to 02/2021 NOVISMART TECH., Wien, Austria

- Engaged to develop a new booking management solution.
- Developed a full-stack JavaScript application with MERN/MEAN stacks.
- Targeted both mobile device and desktop users with React Native.
- Delivered the iterative product to business.

Full Stack Engineer - 07/2015 to 07/2018

ITM HOUSE, Toronto, Canada

- Maintained and improved the client portal React application.
- Implemented workflows and guidelines for code consistency, readability, maintainability, and testability.
- Refactored and upgraded the continuous integration code of our main repository and created a gem to make available to other projects.

Education

Bachelor of Degree in **Computer Science** - 2010 **Vienna University of Technology**, Vienna, Austria 2006 - 2010

Certification

Certified Web and Mobile Application Developer

Provider: SMTP Issued: January 2020